Previously on desperated housewives...
绝望主妇前景提要...
- Does this relationship have a future?
- 我们之间有希望么?
Can't we just keep
我们不能就这样
- Going the way we are?
- 下去么?
Jackson left.
Jackson走了
- Orson's lying to me again.
- Orson又对我撒谎了
Bree made a decision.
Bree下定了决心
- So I think I have to divorce him.
- 所以我决定跟他离婚
Karl signed up.
Karl来报道了
Karl, what are you doing here?
Karl 你在这儿干嘛?
Well, I just enrolled Evan.
哦 我只是带Evan过来
Wow.
哇
- And Susan confessed.
- Susan也坦白了
Mike and I got in a car accident.
我和Mike遇到了车祸
- Mike was driving, right?
- 是Mike开车的吧?
That's what we said,
我们是那么说的
But it wasn't true. He took the blame for me.
但是不是 他帮我顶罪了
On this street,
在这条街上
The bargaining begins at sunrise...
太阳升起后 讨价还价就开始了...
An old woman offers a paperboy a generous tip
一个老太太给送报的男孩丰厚的消费
If he'll throw the paper onto her porch...
只要他把报纸放到她的门廊上...
A wife tells her husband she'll make his favorite dinner
一个妻子告诉她丈夫 会给他做爱吃的晚餐
If he'll bring home roses...
只要他回来的时候带上玫瑰花...
A man tells his neighbor he'll take in his garbage cans
一个男人告诉他邻居他要把垃圾桶搬进去
The day she finally mows her lawn.
在她终于整理她草坪那天
Yes, on wisteria lane,
是的 在紫藤巷上
Everyone knows how to bargain...
每个人都知道怎么讨价还价...
Absolutely everyone.
绝对的
I don't want oatmeal. Can I have pancakes?
我不想吃燕麦片 有煎饼么?
Katherine's not a short order cook, buddy.
Katherine不是厨房工 小子
If she made oatmeal for breakfast, we're having oatmeal.
如果她早餐做燕麦片 那我们就吃这个
I tell you what, M.J. If you finish just half of it,
告诉你 M.J. 如果你吃完一半
I will make candied apples for your sleepover.
你朋友来过夜的时候我就做苹果脯
- I love candy apples.
- 我喜欢苹果脯
She's letting you off easy. You should thank her.
她太宠你了 你要谢谢她
Thank you, Katherine.
谢谢 Katherine
You are so welcome, you sweet thing.
不用谢 小可爱
Dad, are you gonna marry Katherine?
爸爸 你要和Katherine结婚么?
Um...
嗯...
That's, um...
这个 嗯...
I don't know.
我不知道
Why not?
为什么?
Oh, well, oh, because we haven't talked about marriage.
嗯 嗯 因为我们还没有讨论婚姻
Why not?
为什么没有?
M.J., you're being rude.
M.J. 不要没有礼貌
Oh, I'm not offended.
哦 我无所谓
Don't you wanna marry Katherine?
你不想和Katherine结婚么?
Well...
嗯...
I love her.
我爱她
She's absolutely fantastic.
她真的很棒
So why don't you marry her?
那你为什么不和她结婚?
Can you help me out here?
能帮帮我么?
Are you kidding?
你在说笑么?
Buddy, um, when it comes to marriage,
小子 嗯 说到要结婚
The truth is...
是这样的...
Wow. Would you look at the time? I'm late for work.
哇 你看时间? 我要迟到了
We're gonna have to talk about this later.
我们晚点再说
Coward.
胆小鬼
You got that right.
说得好
How'd I do?
我做的怎么样?
You were great.
太棒了
But he didn't answer me.
但他没有回答我
Doesn't matter. Issue's on the table.
没关系 已经提上议程了
Yes, on this street,
是的 在这街上
The negotiating begins at sunrise,
一大早就开始讨价还价
And it doesn't end...
而且到...
Here's the ice cream I promised you.
这是我答应你的冰淇淋
Until someone gets exactly what they want.
有些人找到答案前都不会放弃
Walter Bergen was a divorce lawyer,
Walter Bergen是个离婚律师
And the women who hired him always had something to say
而且雇他的女人对那个要离婚的男人
About the men they were divorcing.
总有话说
He's always talking to his grandmother,
他总是和他奶奶说话
Who died six years ago.
都死了六年了
He spends all his money on hookers,
他把钱全用去招妓了
Who may or may not be women.
男女通吃
He says he needs more money for the children,
他说他要给孩子们更多的钱
And by "children,"
说到"孩子"
I mean racehorses.
我是说赛马
Yes, Walter Bergen thought he had heard it all
是的 Walter Bergen在遇到这顾客说的之前
Until the day when one of his clients actually said...
他以为他听完了...
My husband is a decent man, and I want to do right by him.
我丈夫是很体面的人 我想让他做对的事情
Hmm.
嗯
Women who seek my services rarely take that attitude.
女人寻求我的帮助往往不是这种态度
Well I like to think of myself as a good person.
嗯 我喜欢把自己想成一个好人
I'm sure you are.
我相信你是
And I wouldn't worry about your husband.
而且我不担心你丈夫
The income he'll derive
他该得的餐饮生意的
From his half of the catering business alone should...
一半...
Wait. I'm not planning on giving him half.
等等 我不打算给他一半
It's my business.
那是我打理的
Which you started after you were married.
但是是从结婚以后
That entitles him to half.
那他有权拥有一半
I-I may have overstated things
我 我想重申一下
When I described my husband as a decent man.
当我说我丈夫是个体面的人
He actually has a wide variety of psychological problems.
实际上他有很多心理问题
Mrs. Hodge, it's state law what do you want me to say?
Hodge太太 这是州法律 你想要我说什么?
I want you to say that for $300 an hour,
我想说 这是300美元一小时的
You have some lawyer tricks up your sleeve
你总有些法律手段
To help me protect my business.
来帮助我保住我的事业
Surely you're not asking me to do something criminal?
你确定你不是要我做违法的事情?
Mrs. Hodge, didn't you say
Hodge太太 你有说
You like to think of yourself as a good person?
你想自己是好人么?
Well, clearly, I like to think of myself
嗯 是的 但我更想自己是
As a rich person even more.
个有钱人
Oh! Full house.
哦! 满座
Bree takes the high. Gaby gets the low. Split the pot.
Bree拿到了最高 Gaby拿了最低 洗牌吧
Oh, I hate splitting the pot.
哦 我讨厌洗牌
Well, that's the rule. There's nothing you can do about it.
嗯 这是规矩 没有办法
- So stop bitching.
- 不要抱怨了
Well, you can't talk to me like that.
嗯 你不能跟我那么说话
I am the wife of fairview's latino businessman of the year.
我是今年美景镇的拉丁商人的夫人
Hey! So he finally won?
嘿! 就是他了么?
Yeah. There's gonna be a huge dinner,
是啊 会有个盛大的晚会
And we're taking a picture with the mayor and his wife.
还要和市长 市长夫人照相
Oh, not necessarily. I hear they're getting divorced,
哦 没必要 我听说他们要离婚了
- And it's gonna get ugly.
- 很尴尬的
Really? How do you know?
真的么? 你怎么知道?
The wife hired
他老婆
The sleaziest, most unethical divorce lawyer in town.
雇了这镇上最没有道德的律师
Oh. Who... who's that?
哦 谁... 是谁?
My ex-husband.
我前夫
Oh, right. Karl's a divorce lawyer.
哦 是啊 Karl是离婚律师
Yeah, and a total shark.
是啊 相当猛烈
The worst thing about our divorce
我离婚最糟糕的事情就是
Was that I couldn't hire him to represent me.
我没能请他为我辩护
- But I thought you just split everything done the middle.
- 哦 我以为你们是平均分配的
Oh, not with Karl.
哦 不是和Karl那次
By the time he's done finding loopholes and hiding assets,
在他找到漏洞 移走财产的时候
There's nothing left to split.
没有什么能平均分配的了
You don't say.
你没说
Hey, ladies.
嘿 女士们
Uh, Lynette, ahem.
嗯 Lynette 啊
It's getting kinda late.
有点晚了
- Are you kicking us out, Tom?
- 你想赶我们走么 Tom?
Uh, no. No, just reminding Lynette
啊 不 不 只是提醒下Lynette
That it's, uh, ten minutes till midnight,
嗯 还有10分钟就12点了
Which means ten minutes till tomorrow.
是说马上到明天了
I got it. I'll be right up.
知道了 马上上来
What was that about?
什么意思?
Tom and I are reading this book that suggests
Tom和我看的书上说
Couples make a pact to have sex every night for a month.
一个月里每天性生活能让夫妻更亲密
- Let me guess. Written by a guy?
- 我猜猜 男人写的?
Was his name Carlos Solis?
是叫Carlos Solis么?
We've been having some problems,
我们之间有点问题
So the theory is it creates intimacy and brings you closer.
这个方法只是想制造些亲密 让我们更紧密而已
Is it working?
有用吗?
I've gotta say it is.
我必须得说有用
You become more attuned to each other's needs
当你们俩越来越了解彼此的需要
- and more sensitive to...
- 对... 越来越敏感
Lynette!
Jeez! Two seconds!
天哪! 马上就来!
- We... we should go.
- 我们... 我们该走了
No, we're in our third week. We got this down to a science.
不 我们才第三周 我们那上好
Just deal me out a few hands.
帮我分一下牌
Juanita, hurry up. The bus will be here any minute.
Juanita 快点 校车随时都会到
Be right down!
马上下来!
There's an extra piece of cinnamon toast on the table.
桌上还有另一片肉桂土司面包
Not hungry. Bye!
我不饿 拜拜!
Susan? It's Dave.
Susan? 我是Dave
Hey, remember I was telling you about my buddy
嘿 还记得我说过我有个好朋友
that owns that boat on bass lake?
在贝斯湖上有条船了吗?
Yeah, well, he's not using it this weekend,
是的 他这个周末不要用船
So I thought maybe I'd take you and M.J. fishing.
所以我想带你和M.J.去钓鱼
Yeah, I know it's short notice,
是的 我知道有点突然
But I really wanted to do something to thank you.
但是我真的很想谢谢你
You've been so good to me since Edie died.
Edie死后 你一直关心我
Plus I know M.J. would love it.
而且我知道M.J.会喜欢的
Great. I'm really looking forward to it.
太好了 我真的很期待
Bye.
再见
Hello?
喂?
Oh, hi, principal Hardy. What's up?
哦 嗨 Hardy校长 什么事?
She's wearing what?
她穿着什么?
Now march in there and wipe that stuff off!
现在给我进去把脸上擦干净!
- You don't have to yell.
- 你不必大呼小叫的
Yes, I do. Do you have any idea
我是叫了 你知道不知道
how humiliating it was for me to get that call today?
今天接到那通电话我有多丢脸?
Now every parent in town is gonna think
现在镇上所有的家长都会以为
that I let my 6-year-old wear makeup to school!
我让我6岁的女儿化妆去上学!
And I want my makeup back.
我想拿回我的化妆品
Is it in here?
在这里面吗?
Why do you have this?
为什么你会有这个?
Juanita.
Juanita
I was trying to look like you.
我在试着变得像你
Why?
为什么?
Some girl at school saw you pick me up yesterday
昨天学校的女生看到你来接我
and told me I must be adopted.
还说我一定是领养的
They said I wasn't pretty enough to be your daughter.
他们说我不漂亮 不足以当你的女儿
How's it feeling, Mrs Mccluskey?
感觉怎么样 Mccluskey太太?
I... it's really throbbing. Oh, please hurry.
我... 真的很痛 噢 请快一点
Okay.
好的
Hi there.
嗨
Jackson, hey. You're back.
Jackson 嘿 你回来了
I needed to talk to you.
我得和你谈谈
Why didn't you call?
你为什么不打电话给我?
I wanted to surprise you.
我想给你个惊喜
Well, you did.
是的 你的确是
Ahem.
嗯哼
Oh, uh, right.
哦 呃 对了
Jackson, you remember Mrs. Mccluskey, don't you?
Jackson 你记得Mccluskey太太的 对吗?
Sure. How are you, Mrs. Mccluskey?
当然 你还好吗 Mccluskey太太?
Oh, I'm in agonizing pain. Thanks for asking.
噢 我现在疼痛难忍 谢谢你的关心
I'm taking her to the doctor
我正要带她去看医生
so he can perform a little procedure.
所以他能办一些手续
He's gonna lance a boil on my backside.
他会在我的背上拔火罐
It may rupture any second.
可能会需要些时间
Okay.
好的
I just had my car detailed, so I should probably go.
我刚启动车 我该走了
No problem.
没问题
Uh, when can I see you?
呃 我什么时候能见你?
Um...
呃...
How about dinner tomorrow night?
明天晚餐的时候怎么样?
Sounds great.
听上去不错
If you two want to keep staring at each other,
如果你们俩要一直这样凝视着对方
I can just go lay down on the lawn and die.
我可以躺在草坪上死去
I don't mind.
我不介意的
I'll see you tomorrow.
明天见
Karl.
Karl
Hey, Mike. Heard M.J.'s having a sleepover.
嘿 Mike 听说M.J.在邀请别人来家里过夜
I thought I'd hit you up for an invitation.
我想我请求你的邀请
Aren't you a little old for sleepovers?
你是不是过了去别人家过夜的年纪了?
Cards on the table. I need your help.
摊牌吧 我需要你的帮忙
Evan's one of the only boys in class who wasn't invited,
Evan是班上唯一没被邀请的男孩
And he's really upset.
他真的很难受
Okay, cards on the table. M.J. says Evan's a bully,
好吧 摊牌 M.J.说Evan欺善怕恶
And he doesn't want him at his sleepover.
他不想要他来家里过夜
Well, what if I promise Evan will be on his best behavior?
那好 如果我保证Evan能乖乖的呢?
I'm sorry. It's out of my hands. M.J. finalized his guest list.
对不起 我帮不了你 M.J.的客人名单已经写好了
Well, I think if you check that list again,
我想如果你再检查下名单
You'll notice evan's name's on there.
你会发现Evan的名字在上面
I'm M.J.'s dad,
我是M.J.的爸爸
Not his bouncer.
不是他的保镖
But...
但...
Thanks.
谢谢
Hey, honey. How's your day going?
嘿 宝贝 今天过的怎么样?
Very exciting. Just got back from the grocery store.
非常兴奋 我刚从杂货店回来
It is double coupon day, sorta like the Oscars
今天是双息天 有点像奥斯卡
and the super bowl all rolled into one.
和超级大腕都一起来了
Did you remember to get my, um...
记得帮我买我的 呃...
My special deodorant?
特别除臭剂了吗?
I sure did.
当然记得
Milady's armpits will be aluminum-free.
我太太的腋窝将会没有臭味
- How is your day?
- 你今天过的怎么样?
I'm totally slammed, which is why I'm calling.
我完全崩溃 所以我打电话给你
It looks like I'm gonna be here late tonight,
好像我今晚要待到很晚
And by "late," I mean past midnight.
至于 "很晚" 我的意思是过了午夜
Wait. W-what about our pact?
等等 那我们定的合约呢?
- We'll... Double up tomorrow.
- 我们... 把它加倍到明天
Lynette, I have been looking forward to this all day.
Lynette 我已经期待了一整天了
I know, and I'm really sorry. Listen, I gotta go.
我知道 我真的很抱歉 听着 我得挂了
I will call you later. I love you. Bye.
过会再打给你 我爱你 拜
Tom. What are you doing here? Is everything all right?
Tom 你来这干吗? 出什么事了吗?
Everything's fine.
没什么事
Well, then what are you doing...
那你来这里...
Here?
干嘛?
Oh, no.
噢 不
Are you crazy?
你疯了吗?
Crazy about you, baby.
为你而疯狂 宝贝
But I have so much to do,
但我有很多事要做
And I'm not gonna be done till 2:00 a.m.
凌晨2点前我是做不完的
Possibly 3:00.
可能要到3点了
Whoo! Come on. This is important. Remember what the book said?
喔! 这个很重要 还记得书上是怎么说的?
Every night, no matter what.
无论怎样都要每晚坚持
No, this is a really bad time for me.
不 对我来说这个时候很不合时宜
Mm.
嗯
Well, you did buy me that deodorant. Ooh!
那么 你真的帮我买了除臭剂  噢!
Mmm.
嗯
Lynette, I have Carlos on line two.
Lynette Carlos的电话 2号线
Uh, tell him I'll call right back.
呃 告诉他我马上打回过去
Mm.
嗯
He says it's really important.
他说真的很重要
Hello?
喂?
Hey, Lynette. I'm over here at Capital Consultants,
嘿 Lynette 我现在在资本顾问公司
And the guys have a question.
这些人有一个疑问
- I need you to pull up their account.
- 我要你找下他们的账户
W? I'm kind of busy!
什么? 我有点忙!
Well, the ad has to be at the printer's by noon,
这个广告必须中午前打印好
- So yeah, now.
- 所以是的 现在
Mwah. Mmm.
嗯 嗯
Lynette?
Lynette!
Yes?
嗯?
What's going on? You all right?
怎么回事? 你还好吗?
Sorry. Just had the handyman in here, but he's finished.
对不起 刚有个勤杂工在这 但他打扫完了
Thank you, handyman.
谢谢 勤杂工先生
You're welcome, ma'am.
不客气 女士
So... Carlos...
然后 Carlos...
Where were we?
说到哪了?
- Could I get you something?
- 要喝点什么么?
No, thanks, I don't drink.
谢谢 我不喝酒
Oh, that's right.
哦 这是对的
Glug glug. I remember now.
格拉格 我现在想起来了
I'm bringing you business, Karl. Try not to insult me.
我在跟你谈生意 Karl 别侮辱我
Sorry.
不好意思
So you want to divorce Orson.
所以你是想和Orson离婚
Yes, I know that comes as a surprise.
没错 我知道这是有点意外
Not really. I've met him.
也没有 我见过他
The guy's a stiff.
那男人很死板
Karl, if we move forward,
Karl 如果我们继续谈
I will insist you handle our divorce with dignity.
我很坚持 你必须尊重我的案子
Are you sure?
你确定么?
I don't know of a dignified way to screw a spouse out of money
我不知道为了钱而拆散一对夫妻 还能有什么高尚的方法
That they, by law, are entitled to.
他们在法律上都享有权力的
That is why you're hiring me, right?
这就是聘请我的原因 对么?
I just want to protect what is rightfully mine.
我只想捍卫我法定的权利
Can you help me?
你能帮我么?
Sure.
当然
Lovely.
很好
- I'll make out a check.
- 我给你开张支票
Yeah, not so fast.
很好 但不需要这么快
Uh, I said I could do it, not that I would.
呃 我说我能解决到 但并没有说我愿意帮你
I need a favor.
我需要你的帮忙
Well, what kind of a favor?
呃 帮什么样的忙呢?
M.J. Delfino is having
M.J Delfino会邀请小朋友到
A sleepover at his house in two days.
他家睡两天
My son wasn't invited. Now his feelings are hurt.
我儿子没被邀请 他现在很伤心
So?
所以呢?
So I want you to get my son into that sleepover.
所以我希望你能让我儿子参加那个活动
How would I go about doing that?
我能怎么办呢?
Gosh, I don't know.
上帝啊 我哪儿知道
How would I go about hiding your assets from Orson?
那我又要怎么帮你不让Orson分掉财产呢?
I need your help, Karl. I really do,
我需要你的帮忙 Karl 我真的很需要
But I am not comfortable manipulating a 6-year-old.
但摆布一个六岁的小孩会让我内疚的
Mm-hmm. You know, I had this one client...
嗯哼 知道么我有一个客户...
His wife had been with him since junior high.
他的老婆自从中学就跟他在一起
She supported him through med school,
她支持他上完了医科学校
Gave him three kids and the best years of her life.
为他生了三个孩子 奉献了最宝贵的年华
Once I had done my particular brand of legal magic,
但在我独到的法律手段
He ended up with 90% of the money,
他得到了90%的钱
And she ended up in a studio apartment...
而她只得到了一件公寓套房...
With a roommate.
还有一个舍友
Then again...
那么...
M.J. Does...
M.J 的确...
Love my macaroons.
很喜欢我的杏仁饼干
Sweeties all the other girls are idiots.
亲爱的 其他女孩都是白痴
- You are a gorgeous little girl.
- 你是个迷人的小女孩
You have to say that. You're my dad.
你必须这么说 你是我爸爸
No, it's the truth. You are naturally beautiful.
没有 这是事实 你天生丽质
- Makeup just covers that up.
- 化妆品把你的美都遮盖了
He's right, sweetie. You don't need all that gunk on your face.
他说得对 亲爱的 你根本不需要把那些油腻的东西抹到脸上
- Then why do you wear it?
- 那你为什么要化妆?
Because I'm an adult.
因为我是大人
And besides, I hardly wear any.
而且 我根本就不怎么化妆
Come on, Gaby. Let's try to keep this real.
得了吧 Gaby 别说瞎话
Are you gonna wear makeup when daddy gets his big award?
在爸爸领奖的时候你要化妆么?
Well, it's a big, fancy dinner. Of course.
呃 那是个大型的晚宴 当然要啦
- But that's not fair.
- 但这不公平
Sweetie, you're 6.
亲爱的 你才六岁
There's a lot of things I can do that you don't.
有很多事我能做 但你不能
So you get to look pretty at daddy's party,
所以你能打扮的很漂亮去爸爸的派对
And I have to look like this?
而我就要像这样?
- Hey, I have a great idea.
- 嘿 我有个好主意
Okay, see? Your daddy's got a great idea.
好了 看到没? 你爸爸有个好主意
How about if neither one of you wears makeup to the dinner?
不如今晚的派对你们俩都不化妆?
Okay.
好
No, no, no. Your daddy's just being silly.
不 不 不 你爸有点犯傻
Can I talk to you for a second, silly daddy?
能私下聊聊么 傻爸爸?
Are you a lunatic? I am not walking
你疯了么? 我决不会
- Into a ballroom full of people without my face on.
- 什么都不化 就走进满是人的舞厅的
Come on. This is the perfect opportunity
得了吧 这是个大好的机会
To teach her that beauty's only skin deep.
去教会我们的女儿美貌只是个皮囊
Yeah, well, once you see this skin without foundation,
没错 但你看到没有美貌的皮囊时
- You may want to rethink that.
- 你就会后悔的
Gaby, your daughter is in pain. And don't you love her enough
Gaby 你的女儿正伤心呢  难道你对她的爱就不足以
To put your vanity aside for one night?
让你放下你的虚荣心 就一个晚上?
I was in labor for 20 hours. She still owes me for that!
我干了20个小时的活儿 她还欠我这个人情!
Fine.
好吧
I will make the ultimate sacrifice,
我要做出最大的牺牲
And I will be ugly for my daughter.
为我的女儿变得丑陋
But if she ever needs a kidney...
如果哪天她需要个肾...
Wow. You're really going all out on this sleepover.
哇 你对这个活动还真是全力以赴啊
Although I'm not sure
尽管我还不很确定
That tons of sugar and whistles are a good combination.
这吨糖和哨子会是一个很好的组合
Oh, good point.
哦 提得好
I'll make us some goody bags filled with earplugs and vodka.
我给大家准备了一些充满耳塞和伏特加的糖果袋子
It's great. I'm sure M.J. Will appreciate it.
太好了我相信M.J会喜欢的
I'm sure he will.
我相信他会的
He's a great kid...
他是个好孩子...
And funny.
而且很风趣
That was hilarious the other day,
那天真是很有趣
- When he asked us when we're getting married.
- 当他问我俩什么时候结婚时
I'm glad you thought it was funny.
我很高兴你认为这很有趣
I was tap-dancing my ass off.
我可以很狼狈
No, you were great.
不 你很好
Although...
尽管...
Someday you'll probably have to answer the question.
终有一天你得回答这个问题的
I'm sure he's forgotten by now. You know kids.
我肯定他现在已经忘了  你知道孩子么
Kids are like that.
孩子们都这样
Grown-ups on the other hand...
而大人么...
Not so much.
就不一样了
We're not talking about M.J. Anymore, are we?
我们不会再讨论M.J了 再也不了 对么?
Oh, you want to go run and get your tap shoes?
哦 你想穿着你的踢踏舞鞋逃跑么?
No. No. I'll be completely honest here.
不 不 我在这点上很诚实
Moving in with you is
跟你一起住 是
One of the best decisions I ever made.
我所做的最正确的决定
You make me really, really happy.
你让我 真的真的很快乐
But?
但是?
I've been married before,
我结过婚
And I just don't see myself getting married again.
而且我想我不会再结婚了
Okay.
好吧
Probably not what you wanted to hear.
可能你并不想听
I wanted the truth.
我想知道真相
It's not your fault the truth sucks.
不是你的错 事实糟透了
So could you get the streamers out of the car?
所以你能把彩带从车里拿下来么?
Sure.
当然
Oh, by the way,
哦 顺便说一下
For what it's worth,
你知道什么值得么
I do love you.
我真的很爱你
I've only been working there two months, but I love it.
我只在这儿工作了两个月 但我真的很喜欢这里
And the kids are so cute.
孩子也很可爱
And I get to see M.J. During the day, which is nice.
在白天我可以看见 M.J 这非常好
Uh, you know, uh,
呃 你知道的 呃
For a guy that just had to see me so bad,
对于一个看到我坏的一面的人来说
You... You seem awfully far away.
你... 你似乎不是
I'm sorry.
不好意思
I'm just a little nervous.
我只是有点紧张
I have something...
我有些话...
To ask you, and I don't know how you're gonna react.
想问你 我不知道你会怎么回答
What is it?
什么?
Oh.
哦
This is gonna come out of nowhere, but...
这可能很无里头 但是...
I want you to marry me.
我希望我们能结婚
A-and here's how I came to this. The other day...
这是我会这么想的原因 那一天...
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
I have to go upstairs.
我必须上楼了
Now?
现在?
Susan, are you okay?
Susan你还好么?
I'm fine. I just didn't want you to see me crying.
我没事 我只是不想你看到我流泪
Honey, you didn't let me finish.
宝贝 你没让我说完
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦 对不起
Just, um,
只是 呃
all these months,
这几个月以来
I've been telling myself that I didn't really care about you,
我一直在告诉自己 我并不是真的在乎你
which was easy to do because you left so suddenly.
这是那么简单 因为你离开的那么突然
But I am so lonely.
但是我太孤独了
And as much as I tell myself
尽管我努力的告诉自己
that I like being the strong, single woman on her own,
我要做一个独立的坚强的女人
the truth is,
但事实上
I think about you all the time.
我一直在想着你
And I wanted to call you,
我想打给你
but I thought you'd gotten over me.
但我怕你已经忘掉我了
And to hear that you still love me...
听到你说你还爱着我...
that is just something
这就是
that I really needed to hear right now.
这就是我现在最需要的话
And I want you to know...
我想让你知道...
Oh, God. I want you to know I love you, too.
哦 上帝 我想让你知道 我也爱你
Jackson...
I love you.
我爱你
Jackson?
Oh, God.
哦 上帝
I really wish you'd let me finish.
我真的希望你让我说完
Finish what?
说什么?
Susan, I need you to marry me
Susan 我想你嫁给我
so that Immigration doesn't deport me back to Canada.
那样移民办就不会把我送回加拿大了
The one thing I didn't tell you is that
我没跟你说过
I'm here on a student visa that expired six years ago,
我是用一张六年前就到期的学生签证过来的
and I got a call from the authorities,
我接到了移民局的电话说
so unless I can find somebody that will marry me,
除非我找个人结婚
I'm gonna be in really big trouble.
否则我就真的有大麻烦了
Susan?
Susan, did you hear me?
Susan 你听到了么?
I heard.
我听到了
So...
所以...
What do you say?
你说呢?
Okay. Okay, it was a bad idea.
好吧 好吧 这不是个好主意
Get out or I will kick your ass back to the Canadian border!
滚 不然我一脚把你踹回加拿大!
Ow!
哎哟!
Took a shower, brushed my teeth.
洗个澡 刷个牙
We are good to go.
可以开始了
Mmm.
嗯
Lynette.
Lynette
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
You know, the pact.
你知道的 我们的约定
Oh.
哦
Didn't we already do it tonight?
我们今晚不是做过了么?
No.
没有
Oh, they're all starting to blur.
哦 我都记不清了
Look, I worked till 3:00 a.m. Last night.
听着 我昨晚工作到凌晨3点
I'm exhausted. How about we take a rain check?
我累崩溃了 我们能不能改天再做啊?
- A rain check?
- 改天?
Mm.
嗯
This isn't baseball.
这不是棒球比赛
Every night for 30 days... that's the Law.
一个月要做30个晚上... 这是规定
Tom, I have a 7:00 a.m. meeting.
Tom 我7点还有个会议
How about I take a long lunch,
要不明天你午餐时间来找我
and you do me twice at work tomorrow?
我延长午餐时间 我们做两次?
Come on.
不要
This is important.
这很重要
Okay.
好吧
We'll have sex.
我们做爱吧
But can you make it quick?
但你能不能快点?
Lynette, please.
Lynette 拜托
You can't rush an artist.
别催促一个艺术家
Mmm.
嗯
Morning. Oh, sorry. I don't have time for breakfast.
早 哦 抱歉 我没时间吃早饭了
Good. I didn't make you any.
很好 我本来就没做你的
Oh, okay. Uh, coffee will be fine.
哦 好吧 呃 咖啡就行
Beans are right there. Grab a handful and grind.
咖啡豆就在那 自己抓一把磨碎了去
Is there a problem?
出什么问题了么?
You don't remember?
你不记得了么?
Last night, we were having sex?
昨夜 我们正要做爱?
You fell asleep?
你却睡着了?
After?
做完过后?
During.
做的时候
Oh.
哦
Was it good?
感觉好么?
I didn't finish.
我没做完
God, you ruined our streak, Lynette.
天啊 你破坏了我们之间的气氛 Lynette
I'm sorry. I was exhausted.
对不起 我快累疯了
It's not like I was asking you to scrub a floor.
我又没叫去擦地板那么累
All you had to do was lie there, like you usually do.
你只需要躺在那儿 跟你平常一样
Oh, okay. I'm gonna let that one go, 'cause you're upset.
哦 好吧 我不会再让那样的事情发生了 因为你不高兴了
Well, it's true.
没错
With you being so tired from work lately,
最近你工作累得要死
I'm the one doing all the heavy lifting.
我才是那个做粗活累活的人
Tom, you're being completely irrational.
Tom 你这是无理取闹
We've had sex 23 days straight.
我们这23天都一直有做爱
- I've seen more ceiling than Michelangelo.
- 我看天花板的时间比米开朗基罗都长
We made a commitment, Lynette. The Book says...
我们有约定 Lynette 那本书说...
Oh, would you stop with the Book?
哦 你能不能别再提那本书了?
You bought it at a car wash
你在洗车场买了它
- along with a pack of gum and an air freshener.
- 还有一包口香糖 一瓶空气清新剂
You're right. It's stupid. All my ideas are stupid.
你是对的 我是蠢猪 我所有的主意也都愚不可及
- I should just stick to doing chores.
- 我应该继续做这些家务事
Don't just walk away.
别走
You better get to work, Lynette. You're gonna be late.
你该去上班了 Lynette 不然你要迟到了
Hey. Haven't seen you boys in a while.
嘿 有阵子不见了
There's been a break in the club fire case, Mr. Williams.
俱乐部纵火案有些眉目了 Williams先生
You got a minute?
你有时间么?
Do you know this guy?
你认识这个人么?
No. Who is he?
不 他是谁?
Dr. Samuel Heller, psychiatrist from Boston.
Samuel Heller博士 波士顿来的精神病专家
He's the guy who burned up in the fire.
他就是在大火里被烧死的人
What's a shrink from Boston doing in Fairview?
一个波士顿的心理医生在美景镇做什么?
No idea, but we'd like to find out
不知道 但我们想找出
if anyone knows him or what he was doing there.
有没有人认识他 或者 他来这儿想干什么
- Did you see him backstage?
- 你在后台见过他么?
No, I didn't see anybody.
不 我一个人也没看见
Except Porter Scott.
除了 Porter Scott
Yeah, but I told you. That was a mistake.
是的 但我告诉过你 那只是我弄错了
Do you know a guy named Jackson Braddock?
你认识一个叫Jackson Braddock的家伙吗?
- He was backstage.
- 他当时也在后台
Was he?
是吗?
Yeah, he got locked in the employee men's room
是的 就在起火之前
- right before the fire started.
- 他被锁在了男洗手间里
Well, I don't know anything about that.
这我就不知道了
- Have you talked to him?
- 你们和他聊过了么?
We've been trying,
我们一直在努力
but he left town, and we've been unable to find him.
但他离开镇子了 我们找不到他
- That's a shame.
- 太可惜了
We'll figure it out. Thanks for your time.
我们会弄明白的 感谢你的合作
You bet.
不客气
Hey, Susan. It's Dave.
嘿 Susan 我是Dave
You know, I was thinking I'd pick up you and M.J.
我想在周六早上6点去接你和M.J.
around 6:00 a.m. Saturday for the trip.
然后来个旅行
Yeah. I figured whe earlier we get going, the better.
没错 我觉得越早上路越好
Okay.
好的
Well, hello there, M.J.
嘿 你好 M.J.
I was baking this morning, and like an idiot,
我像个白痴一样 一早都在烤面包
I made too many macaroons.
我做了太多蛋白杏仁饼干
Would you be willing to take one?
你想不想吃一个?
- I would hate to see them go to waste.
- 我可不想看到它们浪费掉
Macaroons are my favorite.
我最爱吃蛋白杏仁饼干了
Oh, really? What a delightful coincidence.
哦 真的么? 真是太巧了
You know, I could bake these for you every week,
我可以每周都给你烤这个
and all I'd need in return is just the tiniest of favors.
你只需要帮我很小的一个忙作为回报就好
What kind of favor?
什么忙呢?
Invite Evan Mayer to your sleepover.
邀请Evan Mayer来你家过夜
I don't like Evan. He's mean.
我不喜欢Evan 他很小气
Oh, no.
哦 不
Deep down, he's just a fragile little boy,
实际上 他只是个希望被别人喜欢
who wants to be liked.
又很敏感的小男孩
He hit me with a dead squirrel.
他曾经用一只死松鼠来打我
Now, M.J., we can find faults with all our friends
这样 M.J. 如果我们挑刺
if we nitpick.
那我们的所有朋友都有缺点
What do you say? Will you invite him?
你觉得怎么样? 你会邀请他吗?
Would you like some ice cream with your macaroons?
你想要一些冰激凌就着杏仁甜饼吃吗?
Beause I could make that happen.
我可以让你吃到
Bree?
I'm late for my golf game.
我打高尔夫球要迟到了
I don't have time to go to the A.T.M.,
没时间去自动取款机
so I took the cash out of your wallet.
所以我从你皮夹里拿了现金
Bye.
再见
M.J., there's someone in my life
M.J. 在我的生活中
who hits me with a dead squirrel
每天都有人
every single day.
用死松鼠来打我
And you are the only one who can help me.
而你是唯一一个可以帮我的人
Please, please invite Evan to your party.
拜托你邀请Evan来参加你的派对
Okay.
好吧
Thank you.
谢谢
Oh, thank you, sweetheart.
哦 谢谢你 小甜心
Boy, the stuff I do for macaroons.
小子 我这样做是为了这些杏仁甜饼
Go away! I... I don't want to talk to you.
走开! 我... 我不想和你说话
Come on. Let me in.
别这样 让我进去
Thanks, but I've reached my maximum allowance
谢了 这礼拜我对丢脸的忍耐
for humiliation this week.
已经达到最大限度了
Listen, I'm sorry you thought it was a real proposal.
听着 我很抱歉让你以为那是真的求婚
I thought I should let people do that.
我觉得你明白我必须这样
Maximum allowance exceeded.
超过了最大限度
What do you want?
你想怎么样?
I wanted to apologize. You have every right to be mad at me.
我想道歉 你完全有权利对我生气
Oh, I'm not mad at you.
哦 我不对你生气
You know, I'm just disappointed in myself.
你知道 我只是对自己很失望
I was a little lonely and a little afraid
我有些孤单 还有些害怕
and... I just did what I always do...
还有... 我只是又在重蹈覆辙...
Let some silly romantic fantasy take over.
沉迷在一些罗曼史奇幻中
I didn't know you still felt that way about me.
我不知道你对我还有那种感觉
I don't.
我没有
This isn't about you.
这不是关于你
Not really.
真的不是
And besides, you moved on.
再说 你也在重新开始
Well, I had to.
嗯 我不得不
You pushed me away.
你抛弃了我
I had to... heal my heart and get over it.
我不得不... 治愈自己的心 并从中恢复过来
This... I mean, this is really the only thing you can do
这... 我的意思是 这真的是你呆在这里唯一能做的事情
to stay here and do your work?
还有你的工作?
Yeah.
是的
I'll help you.
我会帮你的
Really?
真的?
Yeah.
是的
I'll do it. But that's it.
就是帮忙 仅此而已
No love, no sex, just...
没有爱 没有性 只有...
Marriage.
婚姻
No sex?
没有性?
You want people to think this is a real marriage, don't you?
你想让别人觉得这是场真的婚姻 不是吗?
Gaby, come on.
Gaby 快过来
For god sakes, will you take those off? It's 8:00 at night.
看在上帝的份上 你能脱了这吗? 现在是晚上8:00
Oh, fine. As long as you don't mind people thinking
哦 好的 只要你不介意人们以为
you're out on the town with your anemic lesbian sister.
你和你贫血的同性恋姐姐来城里作乐
There's our man of honor.
我们有声望的人来了
Gaby, this is Stephanie.
Gaby 这是Stephanie
- She put this whole banquet together.
- 她组织了整个宴会
Hi. Nice to meet you.
嗨 见到你很高兴
- You're probably wondering why I look like this.
- 你可能奇怪我怎么看起来这个样子
Excuse me?
什么?
I'm not ill. I'm just not wearing any makeup
我没病 我只是没化妆
so I can teach my daughter that beauty's what's on the inside.
这样我可以教育我的女儿 美是种内在的东西
I don't actually look this hideous.
事实上 我没有那么吓人
Okay.
好吧
Will you please stop explaining yourself?
能别再对你自己作解释吗?
- I mean, it was bad enough when you did it with the valet.
- 我是说 你跟服务员解释就已经够糟了
I can't help it.
我忍不住
I don't want people thinking I condone this face.
我不想让人们觉得我能忍受这张脸
I'm gonna go find our table.
我去找找我们的座位
Champagne?
要香槟吗?
Oh, thank you.
哦 谢谢
- I'm not ill. I'm just not wearing any makeup.
- 我没生病 我只是没有化妆
Gaby!
Gotta go.
得走了
Come on, guys. No running in the house.
别这样 伙计们 别在屋子里跑
These candy apples are great.
这个苹果脯很好吃
Can me and Evan have another one?
我和Evan能再吃一些吗?
Well, I better ask Katherine.
嗯 我最好问一下Katherine
Where is Katherine?
Katherine在哪里?
Hey. You're missing all the fun.
嘿 你错过了所有有趣的事
I just got a candied apple out of a kid's hair.
我刚刚在一个孩子头发里发现一个糖渍的苹果
Sounds like you got everything under control.
听起来一切都在你掌控中啊
No, come on down.
没有 快下来
It's not as much fun without you.
没有你就没那么有趣了
Okay.
好的
You were honest with me, so I'm gonna be honest with you.
你对我坦诚以待 我也要向你坦白一切
I got scared.
我很害怕
Of what?
怕什么?
I was hosting a party with this amazing man
我和一个迷人的男人还有他可爱的儿子
and his adorable son,
办这个派对
and we were like the perfect family,
我们像是一个完美的家庭
and then I realized...
然后我意识到...
We're not a family.
我们不是一家人
It could all go away in an instant.
这些可以立刻消逝
Katherine, I'm not leaving.
Katherine 我不会离开
But you're not committing either.
但你也没有承诺啊
Why not, Mike?
为什么没有 Mike?
Is it Susan?
是因为Susan?
You still in love with her?
你还爱着她?
No.
不
No, I've told you that.
不 我已经告诉过你了
Then it must be me.
那肯定是因为我了
Katherine, I love having you in my life.
Katherine 我希望你走进我的生活
I'm just not ready.
只是我还没有准备好
I don't know what else to say.
我不知道其它还能说什么
I'm not trying to get you to say anything.
我不是想让你说什么
I just have to take care of myself.
我不得不照顾好我自己
I should probably go make sure the first floor is still there.
我可能该下去看看底楼是不是还在那
Excuse me. The mayor's about to leave,
打扰一下 市长要走了
and the newspaper wants a photo with him and your family.
报社想拍一张你们和他的照片
Oh, that's so sweet.
哦 太好了
- Tell him no way in hell.
- 告诉他没门
Tell him we'll be right there.
告诉他我们马上过去
The newspaper? Forget it.
报社? 算了吧
Gaby, I do business with the city.
Gaby 我在和这座城市做生意
- I can't just blow off the mayor.
- 我不能不给市长面子
Seriously, we can not allow this to be photographed.
说真的 我们这个样子不能被照下来
Next time there's an epidemic,
下次有传染病的时候
People are gonna think I'm patient zero.
人们会认为我是头号病人
You're not getting out of this.
你避免不了这个
Fine.
好吧
But just so we're clear, you're also latino jerk of the year.
那我们也说清楚 你是年度拉丁混蛋
Come on. Let's go.
拜托 走吧
Oh, can I at least use the bathroom first?
哦 我能先去用下洗手间吗?
Ladies! Attention, please.
女士们! 请注意
I am in a jam, and I need lipstick and eyeliner.
我现在很窘 我需要唇膏和眼线膏
Come on. Chopchop.
快点 就用一下
You can use my makeup.
你可以用我的化妆品
Oh, that doesn't really go with my skin tone.
哦 这真的不适合我的肤质
What do you mean? We have the same coloring.
你什么意思? 我们有相同的肤色
Yeah, it doesn't really go with your skin tone either,
是的 所以那个也不适合你的皮肤
but I can only deal with one disaster at a time.
我一次只能处理一个麻烦
Ooh. Asian girl. Close enough.
噢 亚洲姑娘 你的粉色很接近
Um, I don't think so.
我不觉得
Ugh. Was it the "chop chop" thing? Fine. I'm sorry.
噢 我刚才的口头禅不好? 抱歉
Now can I borrow some blush?
我能借用你的腮红吗?
I don't share cosmetics. I'm sort of a germ freak.
我不和别人共用化妆品 我怕细菌
- Oh, don't worry. I'm as healthy as a horse.
- 别担心 我像健康得像头牛
Really? You look sick.
是吗? 你看上去很病态
That's 'cause I don't have any makeup!
那是因为我没上妆!
I said no. Now leave me alone.
不行 别烦我了
Okay, okay, look. I'm sorry. You're right.
好了好了 很抱歉 你说得对
I never should have asked.
我不应该提这种要求
Oh.
哇
Oh! Hey!
啊! 喂!
Come out now, or I'll call security!
马上出来 否则我叫保安!
You know, for a woman who has a purse full of dinner rolls,
听着 对一个钱袋只有小餐包的人
You sure have a lot of attitude.
你应该有同情心
Oh, good. We're all here.
很好 人都到齐了
By the way, Mrs. Solis, you look absolutely stunning.
Solis夫人 您真是光彩照人
Thank you.
谢谢
Yeah, mom. You look great.
是啊 妈妈 你很漂亮
Okay, big smiles, everyone.
好啦 大家笑一笑
See this?
看?
My third espresso.
第三杯浓咖啡
I'm wired. No way I'm falling asleep tonight.
它令我精神亢奋 今晚不会睡着了
Hey.
喂
How about we throw a pizza on the front lawn,
不如我们丢个批萨到院子里
And when the kids run out to get it,
让孩子们去争抢
We lock the door and do it in every room in the house?
我们趁机锁上门 在每个屋子里都做一次?
Tom, I'm sorry.
Tom 很抱歉
I don't know what else to say.
我不知该说什么了
If you wanna stay mad, I guess you're gonna stay mad.
如果你想生我的气 那你就生气吧
I am not mad, Lynette.
Lynette 我没生气
Then what's wrong?
那怎么了?
You're gonna think it's stupid.
说来你可能会觉得我蠢
Tell me.
说来听听
You want to know why sex
知道为什么最近
has become so important to me lately?
做爱对我来说变得如此重要吗?
Because you are the only thing in my life
因为在我的生活中
that I'm passionate about.
只有你才能让我产生激情
That is so sweet.
那真好
No. No, it's not good, Lynette... not for me, not for you.
不 那不好 Lynette... 对你我来说都不好
I...
我...
I need something else to be excited about.
我需要别的能让我激情澎湃的东西
I thought you wanted to do this, to take a break and stay home.
我以为你很意愿呆在家休息
I did. You know, I figured, the kids are grown...
我本来想 孩子们都已经长大了...
I can take care of the house and the errands,
照料家事会很简单
and it'll be easy, and it is.
确实很简单
It's too damn easy.
简单得真该死
I am finished with my work by noon,
我上午就做完了家事
And then I just sit around,
接着就无所事事
waiting for you to come home.
等着你回家
So...
那么...
What do you want to do? Hmm?
你想做什么呢? 嗯?
What are you passionate about?
什么能让你产生激情?
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm a middle-aged guy,
我已经是个中年人了
And I don't know what I want to do with my life.
却还不知道自己想干什么
I told you it was stupid.
我说过我很蠢
No
不
No.
Hey.
嗨
I know I disappointed you tonight, and I'm really sorry.
今晚我让你很失望 我感动很抱歉
It's okay. I know why you did it.
没关系 我知道你得化妆
I need makeup, too.
我也要化妆
Honey, I know you think being pretty
宝贝 我知道现在你觉得长得漂亮
Seems like the most important thing in the world right now,
是世界上最重要的事
But believe me, it's not.
相信我 不是这样
You were a model.
你当过模特
Yes, I was.
是的
And my whole life,
一直以来
People told me how pretty I was.
人们都在夸我有多漂亮
so you know what?
你知道吗?
I never thought I had to work hard in school
我因为以为自己可以不用好好读书
or work on friendships
不用去交朋友
or my personality... none of it.
不用培养自己的品性... 什么都不用做
And then I stopped modeling,
直到我不做模特的时候
and I realized I didn't have much on the inside.
我才意识到自己没多少内在
And I don't want that for you.
我不希望你重蹈覆辙
I want you to be brave and funny and creative...
我希望你勇敢 幽默 有见地...
to be more than just a shell.
不要做花瓶
I want you to have the whole rich, gooey center.
我希望你有丰富和坚韧的内心
Will you promise to do that for yourself?
你能做到吗?
Okay.
能
When do I get to wear makeup?
我什么时候可以打扮?
I tell you what. You can wear makeup
让我告诉你 当你相信自己不用化妆时就很美时
the day you realize you don't really need it.
你就可以化妆了
Hey.
嗨
I bought M.J. a fishing pole.
我给M.J.买了个鱼竿
I figure I'd teach the little guy how to cast
我想去之前 教小家伙
- before we hit the water.
- 如何掷竿
Oh, my god. We're not gonna be able to make it this weekend.
我的天 我们这周末去不了
I'm kind of...
我可能要...
getting married.
结婚了
What?
什么?
To who?
和谁?
Dave Williams.
Dave Williams
I thought I heard you out here.
我听到你的声音了
Jackson.
Jackson
Just when you thought I was out of the picture, I'm back.
我不声不响又回来了
Since you held up your end of the bargain,
因为你兑现了我的要求
I'm going to hold up mine.
我也会实现你的要求
I'm gonna make sure that you walk away from this marriage
我会确保你全部的生意和财产
with your business and your assets intact.
在这场离婚中毫发无损
Now to accomplish this,
要达到目标
I may need you to lie, stonewall,
我需要你撒谎
Even resort to some outright trickery.
甚至采取欺骗手段
My question is...
我想知道...
Will you be up for that?
你做得到吗?
I used to think of myself as a good person.
我一直认为自己是个好人
If I had a choice, I would always choose the high road.
可以选择的话 我选择光明磊落的行径
Lately I've begun to realize that, um...
最近我开始认识到...
I'm capable of doing whatever needs to be done.
如果形势所逼 我什么都做得出来
You know what that makes you?
知道吗 就凭这点
The perfect client.
你是个完美的客户
On this street,
在美景镇
The bargaining is finished by sundown...
讨价还价随着日落而结束...
A daughter agrees to go to bed early
妈妈同意让女儿穿穿旧礼服
If her mother lets her dress up in her old gowns...
于是女儿同意了早点上床睡觉...
A woman agrees to let her fiance spend the night
未婚夫同意了睡沙发
If he'll agree to sleep on the sofa...
于是女人同意让他在家过夜...
Man allows his lover to get close
情人同意了不再提将来
as long as they don't discuss the future.
于是男人同意与她更亲密
Yes, everyone knows how to bargain on steria lane...
是的 在紫藤巷 人人都知道如何讨价还价...
Hi.
嗨
What are you doing up so late?
这么晚你在这干嘛?
Well, I have a proposition for you.
我有个建议
I'll make you breakfast in the morning
早上我为你做早餐
If you make love to me tonight.
晚上你和我做爱
Why not?
好啊?
But sometimes...
但有时候...
They get more than they bargained for.
他们的目的不仅仅是讨价还价